Oh, yeah.
Today is fr- No, it's Saturday.
Oh, wait a minute.
Yes, today's Saturday.
Honestly, I don't care what day it is, because today is a glorious day.
I'm gonna continue my adventures in Noiter.
I'm actually feeling very optimistic about the runs I'm gonna do today.
I mean, run.
We're not gonna do multiple.
I'm doing one.
And it will be amazing.
How's everybody doing, huh?
Pete the Paper Boat.
I love your name.
This OST brings me back.
Man, the Talos Principle OST is some of my favorite music I've ever heard in video games.
It's just incredible.
There's just something about it.
It puts me in a state of mind I can't quite explain.
You know?
So I totally feel you on that.
The Knife Inventor?
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Good morning, Oliver.
I sprinted out of bed to catch this live stream.
Hey, what's up, Jen?
What time is it at your place?
Is it early or is it like in late morning?
A surprise noise stream, to be sure, but a welcome one.
I know that reference.
Well done.
Also, wait a second.
I need to do this, do that.
Let me just check if all the technical stuff is working.
Test.
Map online.
Back to game.
Back to waiting.
Lovely.
Everything's working.
I have finally set it up, I think, such that I should have an easy time to switch between Slatherspire and Noiter, so I don't have to redo everything.
I've made separate profiles for these games now, so that's why I had to test all the audio last time in Slatherspire.
Because I was a little... I did it the wrong way.
I did it the stupid way.
But yeah, it should be working fine.
Thank you to Vulkall and Frank for resubscribing.
Frank for five months now.
Happy Saturday, KnifeMaker.
Thank you.
I appreciate that.
And Vulkall just lit a knife emote.
You guys love the knives, huh?
Well, I'm glad.
We should have a knife emote.
But isn't there already a knife?
I feel like that's a universal emote.
Is it not?
Or we can have a more special knife?
What else have you got to explore?
Haven't caused a lot of few streams.
Let me think.
What did I do last time?
I actually had a couple of good runs last time.
And I discovered some things.
But honestly, I think I would need to see them again and remember what it was.
Specifically.
But I definitely learned some valuable things last time.
I just don't remember specifically what it was.
But I'm sure I will remember it when I see it.
I mean, I died.
I died for sure, yeah.
But I got all the way to the art last time.
Yeah.
But today is going to be different.
We're going to do even better.
I'm going to continue.
Oh,
man.
Right.
Berserkium.
Starting off with that.
Some bombs and some spark bolts.
A classic, if you will.
Definitely a classic in this game.
The mines.
They call it a mine.
Yes.
Isn't that kind of a great wand?
Holy shit.
It's not bad.
But is that better?
It's not.
Put it here.
Oh, yeah.
Magic arrow time.
And that is Ambrosia.
Berserkium and Ambrosia to start things off.
That is not bad.
Also, did the magic arrow just explode on impact?
No, it was just a coincidence.
Oh, no, we've got the growths.
That's the last thing I want to see.
Oh, hello there.
It's a bit too much fire for my taste.
In fact, I need to find some water.
Kind of important.
There's water here.
But I don't want to get rid of these flasks.
Is that crazy of me?
Maybe I'll drink all this and then take the water.
Yeah, that's actually a great idea.
Water is arguably more important.
With the Berserkium, I also do so much damage.
I should use it while it lasts.
20 damage, baby.
On a single hit.
Even that guy's going to have trouble with me.
Oh, yeah.
Look at that.
Easy peasy.
I feel like I have underrated Berserkium a little bit throughout time.
It is a fantastic chemical.
It shall be imbibed.
It shall go in my system and traverse my organs and bloodstream.
And it's going to feel good.
Much like a drug.
Get rid of that.
Also, does this suddenly dig now that I have Berserkium?
Yeah, not more than usual, I think.
Maybe a bit more.
What do we have here?
Someone said when I was streaming the last time that Neuter is kind of like a card game as well.
And the more I think about it, I guess you could see it that way.
You know, you collect the spells, which may as well be card.
And you just combine them in some order to make things happen.
I can see that point of view.
I've been playing card games without knowing it all this time.
You guys have been indoctrinating me into the card game ways.
It was the plan all along, I think.
And you know what?
I don't mind.
Slimy egg for me.
There's so many mysteries still in this game, like the slimy egg.
Like what is the point of that?
Silver pouch?
Hello.
Just a bunch of silver.
What if we put silver in here?
With water?
But wait, with a Brocha?
Mix it.
Nothing.
Okay.
I still have my recipe list.
I need to update it more.
So far I have two recipes.
I think I have one where I can make polymorphine out of chaotic.
Hold on.
Let me actually see.
This one.
Cookbook.
Blood and flammoxium and oil creates unstable polymorphine.
That's the one.
Right.
I'm not sure that now.
So I betcha there's all kinds of combinations just waiting to be found.
And that's one of the goals for today.
Is to try and find some of those.
But only if the opportunity presents itself, of course.
There's so many other things to prioritize in this game.
Such as not dying, for one.
Holy shit.
All kinds of stuff on that one.
Isn't that kind of a nuts wand?
97 explosive damage.
Wait a minute.
Shuffle?
Oh, hold on.
This is dangerous to shoot.
Yeah, that's very dangerous.
Don't want to be using that.
Oh, here's what I discovered last time.
I can use teleportation to get through the holy mountain.
That's the biggie.
That's the big one.
I just recalled.
And look at this.
A beautiful heart.
Not bad at all, eh?
Uh oh.
That's oil.
Let me just wait for that while I sip.
Okay.
It's gonna take a while.
I think I want to get rid of this wand and that wand.
Basically my starter wands.
I'm gonna get rid of.
Water me.
The way is clear.
Also, the berserkium has worn off.
What's that?
Liquid fire plus oil plus blood.
See, that makes me think maybe that's a combination that works to do something.
Why would that just be in there?
It could just be RNG, I guess.
Still, let's put this down gently.
Grab that.
Let's try and... Oh, it's almost empty.
Oh, never mind then.
But I will put it down here.
Of course, it's just gonna burn because of oil and fire.
I don't know what I expected.
Speaking of fire, I wonder if you can add that to a combination of liquids, sort of like boiling in real life.
You know, like you boil some mix of ingredients and something happens, some chemical reaction happens.
That wouldn't take place with lower temperatures.
I wonder if stuff like that is actually a thing.
Because that would be kind of crazy.
Love kicking things.
Get rid of all this.
Also, I'm not jinxing anything today.
I have decided not to jinx anything.
I'm past that.
I'm not gonna do that anymore.
Okay, 400 goldies.
I should go grab the tablet.
What's going on in there?
A heart, maybe?
No, it doesn't look like it.
I think the gold is long gone.
You there.
I guess I'll bomb my way in.
Shit.
Actually, we're fine.
I was hoping that would put it on fire.
Or set it on fire.
Can't speak English.
Nice, nice, nice.
Okay, so now we're back up here.
Oi.
Oh, that's a lot of oil.
Oh, no.
Matilda.
Oh, shit.
Yeah, now we definitely need the tablet.
And we gotta be precise with it too.
Sure, give me that.
We'll replace that one bomb we used.
Wait, he's dead.
Oh, thank God.
Hopefully, the worm didn't go too far down and anger the gods.
It doesn't look like it.
But you never know.
Also, this thing is kind of a formidable enemy.
God damn.
But also has a formidable reward when you kill it.
Balanced as all things should be.
In the end, the universe tends to unfold as it should.
Whoop.
Polymorphine and a lot of it.
No, thanks.
Should I just bomb my way through here?
I think I will.
While I check up up here.
Oh, look at that.
You know what?
Nah, I'm just gonna kill it normally.
I was gonna try to be fancy with a bomb, but it's not worth it.
Damn, monies.
Nah, stop growing.
It's poison.
Oh, no.
That was about to be really bad.
But everything's fine.
Actually, still at ADHP.
We're doing okay.
We still have a bit of time.
You know what?
I'm gonna bomb that.
Shit.
Nah, okay, whatever.
You get to live.
Don't wanna bother with you.
And dude, we gotta translate some stuff today.
Well, if we find something to translate, of course.
Should I just do some damage to someone?
I saw a damage number just now.
Very weird.
Can I not get up there?
Well, shit.
That's unreal.
Let me bomb it.
These flowers are fucking with me.
I think I'm just gonna go through.
I have my tablet.
I have Ambrosia.
Although it would be kinda cool if I could find some teleportation.
Yeah, you know what?
Let's go all the way west first, because I don't think I explored there yet completely.
So we go west first.
Double check if we didn't miss any hearts or something.
This is a precarious spot.
Actually, this is a big cauldron, basically.
Let me experiment.
Ambrosia.
And silver.
I don't think it does anything.
Oh, I couldn't have dodged that one.
Oh, that's bad, that's bad.
Can't go that way.
Very unfortunate positioning there.
You shall die, though.
Look at all that oil.
That's more silver.
Should I pick that up, maybe?
I can pick it up.
Got it.
I have no more bombs.
So fuck.
How do I go west?
I guess I go higher up and then turn left.
We also need a way of digging.
Otherwise, the next level is not gonna be too much fun.
The digging is pretty much required there.
Ah, here we go, here we go.
Okay.
I have not been over here.
Perfect.
Whoa.
You know, you could use these guys to dig through brickwork if you're smart about it.
If you can, like, guide them down and have them shoot at you.
Because it will dissolve brickwork.
That is the next level strategy you could apply in a pinch.
Not that I need it now, but... Oh, no, we're actually kind of low on HP.
This is maybe a bit too dangerous.
Maybe I reached the point where I need to go.
Yeah.
Yeah, we gotta leave, we gotta leave.
It's as simple as that.
Go.
Okay, not bad.
I would say that was solid.
6 out of 10.
No, 7 out of 10 on that first level.
Always cast Earthquake and this is... I forgot what that is.
That's Homebringer.
Holy Shuffle ones, man.
The only non-shuffle is this one and that is Horizontal Path, but increases its damage.
I don't like that.
Because it's being applied at the very beginning.
Hey.
So here's the thing.
This right here, this perk is the perk you would take if you know you're going to get a long run.
But this one is the one you take to increase your chances of getting a good run.
So I'm taking that.
I could gamble, but I'm not gonna.
Because it has bitten me in the ass so many times in the past, trying to gamble like that.
I'm doing the... Smart thing here.
Okay, so damage wise.
We have a magic arrow.
That's not bad.
Let me see if any of these ones are decent, even if they're shuffle.
That one is not too bad.
Has a low cast delay and recharge.
I'm buying it.
We don't want these, I don't think.
Let's put that there.
We could also put burning trail and... No, we don't want fire.
Fire is bad.
This one is cool.
These ones are pretty cool.
Could do spark bolts.
No, it's shuffle, so.
Although... Wait a minute.
That's not terrible.
It's like decent.
So here's the thing.
Can I... Can I...
Heavy spread a dummy?
Do I have a dummy?
I do have these actually.
How good is this again?
Whoa!
Right.
They drop immediately.
Okay.
That is right.
I remember now.
I guess it's nice to drop them on enemies, you go like this.
You know, that could work.
But yeah, for now I think this is fine.
None of these affect anything.
I could do...
No, don't do that.
Although...
Hold on a second, I could do this.
Like, it seems a little bit scuffed.
But the idea is to get the magic arrow to do some damage, right?
That's a little bit weird.
Point fit.
Let me see this one.
No.
I gotta go with that.
That's the main damage.
The rest is meh.
Could get a light.
And...
Fireball orbit.
I don't think I want any of these.
Maybe I want this one.
Just because it has a potential way of digging.
Right?
And it has some of these triplicates.
Triple scatter spell.
So that one...
I think...
If I shoot this... Oh, dude.
I make him mad.
I shoot it up here.
I collapse things on him.
Let's just have a backup in case we need to get out.
I guess I could stand over here and wait.
No, because if I go up here, then the whole idea is lost anyway.
The idea is I need to find a way out of here.
Nah, I don't think there's a decent way to get out of here right now.
Unless I'm smart about this.
Hold on.
So this always casts the earthquake.
I could...
Just... Okay, here's the plan.
I'm going to earthquake someone over here.
Make him mad.
He's going to spawn.
I'm going to shoot up here.
He's going to drop things on him.
And maybe I don't get him.
And if that's the case, I try to run past and get out of here.
But it's going to be a little bit scuffed.
Or I wait here.
And if I don't kill him immediately, I leave.
That's probably the better way of doing it.
Yeah, so I'm going to...
Make him mad by shooting here.
Oh,
he's...
Oh no.
Shit, shit, shit.
Come on, please die, please die.
Okay.
Yes!
Oh my goodness!
That's fantastic.
Get the gold, get the gold, get the gold.
Quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick.
Come on, get in, get in.
No!
Ah, whatever.
Fuck.
Okay.
Let me see if I can dig with this.
Actually, that works pretty well.
Oh yeah, that's good.
That's really good.
Very nice.
Found another strategy against Stuart.
Heck yeah, dude.
Um...
Yeah, we're good.
How do I...
Wait, how do I get out?
I need to...
Shit!
I knew that was going to happen.
I fucking saw that one coming.
Okay, at least I can get up here now.
I just want to get to a safe place before I do this.
Collapse everything there.
Yes, and now we collapse like that.
This should be enough.
Yep!
A bit of a violent method, but it works.
Oh man.
But the good news is we can go back now and change our wands.
That's actually huge.
So I think it may have been worth it.
But if I find a piece with gods, I'm definitely taking this though.
That's just like such a good perk.
A wand!
That's a digging wand.
Actually, so is this.
Technically.
But it does shoot in a formation bifurcated.
Oh, and it has fire on it too.
I don't think I like that.
Because that means it can't dig, right?
Yeah, it's like it.
Yeah, it doesn't work.
Oh, that's right!
We heal!
Okay, this time I cannot forget what perks I have.
I made a huge blunder with that last time.
Not today, baby.
Last time I picked up vampirism and forgot I had it.
It was actually insane.
I remember now.
I think I had that memory repressed.
That's got to be the only explanation there.
Can I dig with this here?
Kinda.
I don't mind using these.
Whoops.
That's good enough.
Okay.
Not bad.
Is that water?
It is!
Lovely.
Release the water.
And nothing...
Oh, there's a chest!
I see the chest, but we can't get in there probably.
That does not look like... no.
Cannot get in there.
But we had a backup chest here.
Whoa!
Feels good to be annoyed again, actually.
Been a while.
Damn it!
I don't want that.
I want a heart!
Honestly, I couldn't care less about these spell refreshers in the early game like this.
Ah, this...
I'm not getting in there, am I?
Or maybe I am.
Yes, I am!
Lovely!
Chainsaws!
Now we're talking!
Fuck yeah, and I can also use that to heal.
In fact, I could even go back now and probably make my wand even better.
What am I limited by in this one?
Okay, I'm limited by recharge, which is perfect, because that's what these reduce.
Lovely!
That's lovely, that.
In fact, I'm gonna make my way back immediately.
It is such a big deal.
Although it is kind of sad to waste this healing potential there, so maybe I'll explore a bit more and then go back when I need some healing.
Man, I can't hit anything, it's insane.
My aim is terrible.
Okay, much better, much better.
Water that.
Ah, ah, ah.
Nice.
And a shop!
I don't think I like any of these.
So stuff like this and this, I think it could be really nice if you have unlimited spells and you have homing.
Think about it.
It's basically like a rock that also explodes, right?
No, it's bouncing off.
Ah, the worst digging wand in the history of digging wands.
I need to destroy that.
No, I don't, I don't, I don't.
Ow!
What?
How?
You shot me through the wall!
This guy has a million HP.
See, now I can use this.
Full HP.
Oh, wait a minute.
The chainsaw does actually dig, but it also heals, so let's not use it quite yet.
Gotta wait a bit more.
Water.
Nice.
A hoodlum!
I sense something in there.
My senses are tingling.
I just need something to dig with.
Don't want to use my chainsaw just yet.
Need it for healing.
What's going on up there?
Heart!
Very nice.
That's big.
Did this guy always make this sound when they shoot?
I feel like that's new.
Maybe there's been an update.
When they go poof, poof.
Maybe I just never noticed.
Getting all the money here.
Whoa!
Oh, but you can't look up.
You're kind of dumb in that way.
Whoa, that was a bit too close.
Don't want to tempt fate.
Come here.
Yep.
Nah.
That gold... I don't care about the gold.
Okay, I have to carry it a little bit.
I carry the minimal necessary amount.
Burn it.
No, don't burn me.
The chainsaw.
Okay, what if I chainsaw this?
Oh, okay.
The digging is decent actually in...
coal.
And this is just the chainsaw.
Wait a minute, how good is this wand?
The what?
There should still be 0.2 seconds of cast delay, but it feels much faster.
Very intriguing.
All right, let's go up here.
The next wand I find in here that has something nice on it, I'm going back.
And then I'm going to tinker.
Actually, the fungal caverns is an ideal place to explore with the perk we have.
There's so many wands there.
Oh, I'm out of water.
That's bad.
That's kind of bad.
I'm going to find some more.
I think I just hit something.
I killed it.
It was a rat.
Insane aim.
Here we are.
Oh no, it's one of those guys.
He's the one who teleports.
But he's not the one who switches places with me when I hit him.
There's a difference apparently.
So this guy is shooting blue balls and he bleeds teleportation.
The other guy, I'm not quite sure.
We gotta pay attention.
There's all this toxic rock.
Percircium.
Ooh, that's actually...
kind of nice.
Levitation.
We don't drink all of this.
We could also get high.
Ooh, I'm tempted now.
It's a bit of a risk, but it is early, so...
It's kind of whatever, right?
Ah!
God damn, these guys are scary.
The totes do not fuck around.
They always surprise me with the damage they do.
Where are all my promised wands?
I feel like this is not what I was promised.
He's a friend.
Oh, wait, what?
Why are you shooting me?
Oh, you're shooting that guy.
Ah, the water's bad.
Ooh.
Nice.
Solid.
Oh, no, that's a teleporter.
I see the projectiles.
Oh, got him.
Nice!
Percircium for the win.
Ooh, he's my friend, but he has a wand.
That's scary.
Oh, look at all the gold.
No!
There's a great opportunity to increase my net worth.
And we see ble- Oh, this guy's also a friend.
You're not a friend.
Wait, why are they all friends?
What the hell's going on here?
Glitter bomb?
Oh, that's totally fine.
That's totally fine.
I will gladly throw a couple of those to heal.
There's actually very little gravity on these when you shoot them.
Actually, not a bad weapon.
I might just keep that.
Yeah.
This one we can throw away for now.
Oh, is that pheromone?
It's gotta be.
Yeah.
That explains why everyone is my friend.
They were bathing in it.
And there's a brochure up there, and there's the dude with the wand.
We gotta be really careful about him.
Can I dig with this?
I wonder.
I- Yeah, kinda.
But it's not easy.
Oh, shit, shit!
Oh, no, don't shoot me.
Where are we?
Alright, take it easy.
Take it easy.
There's a heart.
Very nice.
I see a dude down there.
Where's this man down here?
Oh, that doesn't go very far.
Let's stay back a bit here.
Oh, shit, shit, shit.
That's bad, that's bad, that's bad.
Wrong way.
Look at these projectiles.
It's really fun.
Ah, he's up there.
He's- Oh, I have an idea, I have an idea, I have an idea.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
I'm invisible!
Okay, there we go, there we go.
Ah, fuck!
Ah, remember.
Just kill him.
Very good.
Okay, okay.
It's okay.
So this dude up here had a wand, but it wasn't very exciting, I don't think.
And he probably already used all the heal in it.
But I'll try it anyway.
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
Okay, I still heal, awesome.
Look at the recharge on this.
It's horrendous.
Almost full HP.
Okay, that was solid.
All right.
What is that?
Chaos Die!
Oh, fuck!
I was drowning just now.
Or suffocating.
Ah, we gotta check out what the fuck that Chaos Die is.
I love the sound of that!
Or do I?
Actually, I'm not sure.
Don't hit me with that.
I think that's the one that makes me blind.
I still have some bombs.
If I bounce it?
Ah, fuck.
Oh, that works!
Come on, dude.
Asshole.
Oh my god.
This guy has so much HP, what the hell.
Okay, okay.
I think so.
Oh, this is not water.
It's invisiblium.
Get the heart.
How do I get up there?
I can most likely dig with these if I'm being smart about it here.
Let's see.
Yes.
That's how I'm gonna get in.
That's how the light gets in.
There's a crack in everything.
Whoa!
Okay, that was a bit scary.
Let's be careful.
Wait a minute.
Does charm make me immune to my own damage?
Oh, hold on.
I think I may have discovered something big here.
I don't dare test that in detail right now, but actually maybe I do dare.
I'm not sure.
This is gonna be a little difficult.
Oh, okay.
I still take damage.
Also, I'm out now.
Should have seen that coming.
But I do have this.
But it's not gonna go through rock.
But maybe we don't need to.
Oh, actually it is!
Oh, never mind.
I cast a die and a bunch of mushrooms came out.
Whoa!
All right.
What happens next?
Ooh.
Okay.
What the fuck?
How have I never seen this?
Maybe the game did get updated and some new stuff was added.
Can it spawn a heart or something for me?
Can it do something good at least?
This is actually the scariest thing you can do.
I'm tempted to try and pick it up or kick it.
But I guess kicking it will also roll the die.
They're gonna explode!
Yep.
Maybe just leave them.
I
just want to try a bit more here.
Actually, yeah, just...
Hey!
That's one way to kill them.
Okay.
So we tried two, we tried three.
Four is the spark bolt.
Oh, what?
Whoa!
That was like a double!
It did two things at once.
This is fun.
Can I pick it up?
Cannot pick chaos die.
Please get rid of...
Oh, whoa!
Really?
No shit, Sherlock.
I can actually take it with me.
Roll it for various prices.
I feel like...
I don't...
Hmm, prices?
Doubt on the prices part.
But I will try to throw it and see if it still rolls if I throw it.
Oh!
It doesn't...
Wow, the dice doesn't roll when you throw it.
That's kind of...
counterintuitive.
But I guess you've got to shoot it.
Will it work as a...
in the same way a tablet will work?
Let me try again.
Oh, it does work!
Okay, okay, okay.
All right, all right.
It's actually pretty cool.
Roll it!
Wait, what happened?
Oh, it spawned this guy?
No, it spawned a bunch of small ones.
I like the chaos die.
See ya!
Unfortunately, they don't spawn any gold.
The mushrooms that are spawned with the chaos die.
Bro, you have HP up the wazoo here.
You know what?
His explosion ducked through the dense rock.
I feel like that's a big deal.
Okay, I can probably use this here.
Also to kill this frog!
Dang you!
Let me take this with me.
Oh, I didn't see you!
Bastard.
Go to hell.
Asshole.
Okay, what do I waste my travel here for?
A bunch of energy spheres.
I don't like that.
I need energy orbs.
Although, I guess it's better than this and I can use it to heal, so...
It's not the worst.
Spells per cast 11, though.
That's a bit...
This will do a lot of damage.
If I find something, I will just go like...
And they will die.
Oh, these guys blend into the environment a little bit.
I'm gonna try this big ass attack on them.
Oh, it didn't do that much.
I'll burn alive.
Oh, what?
Oh.
I guess I am shooting fire.
That explains this.
Okay!
Let's get high.
I see a bunch of shrooms here.
And we needed like 300 for this, I think.
Or 220 or something.
Let's see what it says.
You hear the word silver echoing and shifting in colors.
No, wait.
Something else has become silver.
Right, that's how that works.
I can never remember that.
It's actually, it's the biggest blind spot of my brain.
It is kind of hilarious.
Because it would have said transformed here, no?
Plus grass.
So here's the thing.
I think I need to get high three times.
And then I need to come here with a...
demon eye.
That is my current theory on the little puzzle we have going on in this place.
So maybe I'll just do that.
I'm gonna get high three times.
Because maybe we don't even need the demon eye.
Maybe...
Oh, shit!
Be careful, be careful.
Why am I stuck?
I can't...
Oh, there's a little pixel there.
Get out of my sight.
Okay, so it's time for me to get rid of this invisiblium.
Do I really want to transport this chaos die around?
Yeah, I do.
Wait a minute.
How did...
How did this just get transformed into water?
This was full of invisiblium just before.
I have...
Okay, so maybe if...
Okay, you know what?
Maybe if you mix water with invisiblium, maybe it just becomes water.
Maybe it's as simple as that.
That would explain it.
And the way I get out of here is to do this.
Okay.
I see you there, you little fat bastard.
What is the best way to deal with you?
Okay, you're coming here.
I will murder all your children, too.
Women and the children will fall to my saber.
Man, this is actually not going terribly.
Let me grab some money there.
We're chilling.
That's the power of the wand experimenter.
It just gives you so much room for mistakes, you know, which is such a big deal in this game.
The more second chances, third, fourth, fifth or sixth chances you get, the bigger chance of success.
And it makes a lot of sense.
There we go.
Now, let me just go around.
No, go down here.
Man, the chainsaw is not to be traveled with.
It can dig in the right circumstances.
And I've been here, it seems.
So let's just go further down.
It may be time to move on.
No, no, we got to get high.
Yeah, let's go get high again.
Let's see if it works now.
Also, almost 2k gold.
This is actually great.
Level two here.
Just fantastic.
What I really need right now is a trigger.
With my chainsaws, I can make magic happen with that.
Give me a dozen triggers and I can do anything.
Look at this.
Very nice.
We've been super lucky here.
This is going splendid.
Wasn't there also a shop here or was that somewhere else?
What's that?
I wonder what this was before.
But you know what, I bet it's good.
This couldn't have been good what was here.
I'm just imagining it was a bad thing that was there.
Alright, let's find a good collection of mushrooms here.
This seems good up there.
Now hold on, there's also some... Is that levitation or is it...
It is, okay, so let's find them.
Heat.
We're getting high in here.
Let's see, it's 200 enough.
200.
Let's wait a bit.
It is!
Again?
Another thing became diamond.
What has become diamond?
No, wait, it was silver before.
Oh, right.
In my mind, I'm like, silver or diamond, they kind of look similar.
I want to get to that wand in there.
It's pissing me off that I can't get in.
Damn it.
Teleportation!
Didn't mean to do that.
Actually, maybe this is okay.
Oh yeah, I haven't been here.
Hey, that was a happy little accident.
Oh yeah!
And a wand and everything, beautiful.
Don't, don't, don't, don't do whatever it is you're trying to do here.
So we're actually at the top here.
A wand?
That is not a bad wand at all, look at the stats on that.
Nine... capacity as well.
And some bombs.
Yay, sick!
And here we are, look!
Actually, dude, we can, we can use that to translate.
If we have some missing stuff.
Uh oh, uh oh, uh oh.
That guy's kind of scary.
How should I deal with him?
I guess I have a missile.
Oh!
Did you die from that?
You did not even die from that.
There we go.
Much better.
Awesome.
So hold on, I'm gonna get ready here with my phone.
Gotta take a picture of this.
So this is...
Ah, hold on, I was too slow.
Before and...
After.
Maybe I already checked this one, I have to look at my pictures here.
Let me just double check I didn't do this twice.
Uh, I don't think I have...
done this one.
No, this is, no, I haven't done this one.
Very cool.
So I am going to...
actually...
switch to this one.
Uh, we are missing...
We
are missing A, B, C, D, E, F, K, O, E, J.
Is there a J here?
Let's see.
Book of guidance.
Escape our predicament.
They felt our understanding of this world was to be forbidden.
They hid something here in this room.
But I like the ability to truly see what is here.
Oh man, I am getting that ability today.
I will see what is in here.
I will solve the mystery.
But I won't figure out what J is just yet.
Actually, we got most of the capitals here.
Let me see, F, K, O, E, L, C, O, L, M, N, O, P, Q.
We don't have Q.
There is no Q in here.
There is no X either.
Alright, well...
I probably missed something just now, but that's okay.
That's good.
We got some nice wands out of this.
Let's try and get high again.
Oh!
The brother!
Nice!
This wand is really good at dealing with those guys.
Wait, I am going to destroy some of that.
Nice!
Okay.
Drink, drink, drink, drink.
Okay, this should be enough.
Let's see.
The third time, baby.
Oh, wait, I didn't wait long enough.
I have to wait longer.
Oh, I am tripping balls now, though.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
The funny thing is, when you get high and you actually do the transformation, you actually become sober again.
But if you fail it, you will stay this way.
There is a wand in there.
I want it.
Hold on, what is this stuff down here?
Silver transform vomit.
There is vomit everywhere!
I have been at work here.
The sign of a true...
wizard.
I am doing surprisingly well against these little fools.
I have much bigger trouble against these guys normally.
Actually, you know what?
That is for you.
Here you go.
Much better.
In fact, they all sort of dodged it.
Okay.
Oh, that wand is not bad either.
I am taking it.
Don't even care... Wait, am I...
Whoa!
Oh, wait, no.
I thought I was immune to toxic rock while I was high.
I thought I just discovered something incredible.
But that is not the case.
Levitation...
Broken wand.
You know what?
I will take that.
I will get rid of this weird ass chaos die.
What is it going to do down there?
Oh!
Okay, that was a bit scary.
Everything is fine though.
Not the greatest wand.
But...
0.2, 0.47.
I like it more than this.
Yep.
I do.
Let me see how it performs.
It is okay.
Also, I should have done that just now.
I forgot that it was healing.
So, I wasted some healing there.
That is okay.
Whatever.
I got to use my damage, right?
So...
Uh-oh.
Let's check if enough time has passed now.
Micebleum.
I got to find a good collection of fungi here.
That looks good down there.
Look at that.
Where is all that?
Oh!
Uh-oh.
That is poison.
Uh, yeah.
Just eat it.
Please let it...
Let it...
Let it happen.
Over 200.
Let's go.
Oh, yeah.
Acid.
Oh, no.
Uh-oh.
Mmm.
Yo, look at all this!
Holy fuck!
That is a huge mountain of fungus.
Okay, now I want to go back to, uh...
the book.
Just briefly.
I don't think anything is going to happen, though.
Because I don't have the demon eye.
But, you know, since I'm here...
I may as well.
So, it was somewhere up here, I believe.
Actually, there is another broken wand there!
Look!
Hello!
Uh, that is going to take forever.
Let me go this way.
I'll get rid of this pouch.
And there's a wand in here.
What the hell?
Whoa!
Minus .08?
Oh, but the recharge time is...
horrible.
No, I don't want that.
I will take this, though.
Hold on.
What's that again?
Powerful lightning as it bounces.
I'm trying to see...
what happened to the acid.
No, I definitely need the...
demon eye here.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm going to write that down.
So, we should have like a little extra...
nodes area here, just for a current run.
So, I'm going to write...
current run.
Whoops.
We need to do...
get...
demon eye.
And bring...
to the fungal...
caverns.
Nice.
Back we go.
Okay.
It's time to leave this place.
Man, this was a great fungal caverns.
Holy crap.
Can't be mad about that.
Watch this.
That's how you go fast.
That was a bit risky, actually.
I don't know why I just did that.
I want to get to the wand.
I can't get to it.
That's fine.
So, there was nothing of value in the...
holy mountain I came from.
So, I may as well just jump down immediately through this.
Yeah.
Go.
We do not heal.
We save it.
Oh, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
I forgot about this.
Oh,
I forgot about it.
Oh, no.
I have ambrosia.
I'm going to escape.
Wait, hold on.
Let me quickly check what's on the wand.
Worst case, we ambrosia and get out.
Okay, we can pause like this.
That's good.
In fact, I should probably...
Let me think.
Quick.
Magisphere.
Return.
Bombs.
Oh, no.
There's nothing.
Let me see.
Dopple.
Jesus.
Maybe the missile is my best bet here.
I want to remove this because I'm scared of it.
I like this wand, though.
I'm just going to...
Actually, wait a minute.
I can't think.
There's too much pressure.
I can plan my wand right here and then quickly make it.
What do I want to use as my base?
Probably this one.
So I get rid of these.
I put in...
Well, I guess I put in triplicate bolts and chainsaws.
But in...
In the trip...
In these ones.
Oh, fuck, fuck, fuck!
Oh, no.
See ya, buddy!
Oh, okay, thanks.
Thanks.
Thanks for that.
What do we got?
I don't like any of this.
I'm leaving.
I completely forgot about that shit, man.
Completely forgot about it.
Fuck!
Why didn't I think?
I shouldn't have fucking angered the gods.
What a mistake that was.
Oh, man.
I gotta get rid of this dude.
But I can't change...
Wait, what?
Oh, he died.
Hey!
That's great!
Nope.
I will re-rule.
Boink.
What do I get?
Is that...
No, wait, wait.
Aw, man.
That was fooled for a minute there.
Oh, but hold on.
That is a good one.
Perk lottery.
Boing.
Ooh.
You know what?
Give me the greed.
Money is important, actually.
Yeah, okay.
Well, the good news is we can still heal when we find wands, so we will have to...
Hmm.
If I can find something to dig through, I can get back up and change my wands in the first holy mountain.
So I shall be on the lookout for something that can dig.
That's my current plan.
In fact...
This is sort of...
There's a bit of...
Yeah.
It's a good start.
Just need a bit of digging capabilities here.
And that's the plan.
Then we go back and maximize our potential in the first holy mountain.
And then we remember...
That Stuart is gonna be waiting in the next holy mountain as well.
The hell is that?
Oh, it's brass.
It looked like a wand.
Uh-oh.
No!
Okay, that works.
That's actually a great...
Oh, shit button.
Kind of nice that there's light on this.
Come to me.
Whoa!
Taking a bit too much damage here.
The wand!
Heh heh.
Acid balls.
Nah, I'm good fam.
Also, I am gonna change these.
Whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop.
That's scary.
Wow!
What a shot!
Threading the needle there.
I'm in big trouble here.
I need to missile this fool.
Let's kill them all.
Survival comes first.
Ammo comes second.
It's actually a solid weapon that I have here.
Oh, we...
Wait, what?
Oh, that is the, um...
What should I call it?
No, don't kill me!
No!
Fuck!
These guys are insane!
Oh man, what a death.
You know what?
The only reason I died there is because I forgot about Stuart, man.
That was such a crucial mistake.
It's insane.
Ah.
I need peace with the gods immediately.
Somehow, you know what I hate about those enemies I just fought?
Like they shoot these flaming balls in the arcs.
And they just always somehow hit their mark.
I don't understand.
My brain cannot dodge that sort of projectile.
It's just so counterintuitive to dodge those for me.
Oh, there's actually one in there.
And one here.
That's dope.
Although only three slots.
So, not really anything special.
This is gonna release fire, but you know what?
I don't care.
Oh no!
Get up!
Oh, that went better than expected.
I thought I was dead for sure.
I don't know where that electricity came from.
I saw the fire symbol, but...
Yeah, that was a bummer there.
Whoopsie!
Don't.
No, that's not water.
Is it?
Oh, it's swamp.
Okay, that's fine.
I thought I just poisoned myself.
There we go.
Ah, can't go that way.
Oh, he has a wand.
Wait, is that a torch?
That's just a torch.
Yeah.
I'll take it.
God, man, that was such a good run.
We had so much HP, found so many hearts so early on, it was immaculate.
But
then...
Stewart showed up as always.
The fucking party pooper he is.
He's like, fun detected, eliminate!
Uh, yeah, okay.
No!
Don't burn.
I'm way too low HP here.
I may actually have to go through a portal, but...
When you start going through portals at this point so early, you know you're fucked.
You know, you know it's just over.
That's been my experience so far.
So we have to push it a little further here.
I can't go through it just yet.
It's not gonna be okay.
Definitely need some money here.
At the very least.
And I see a wand.
This could be nice.
Nah.
Terrible.
Nobody wants puff of air.
I think I may have changed my mind.
I think the spitter bolt may be my favorite starter.
Spell and not the energy sphere.
It just does so much damage.
It's a little bit short range, but that doesn't matter usually in this place.
It shoots so fast.
It's quick.
It's straight line shots.
It's just lovely.
Look at that.
It's easy to kill things with it.
Just a pleasure.
Blow it.
Oh, you know what I'm gonna do?
If I find the levitation.
Or something.
I'm gonna go grab the demon eye from the get go here.
Because I wanna get high three times again.
We gotta test that.
But I need something to come to the other side of the tree.
At chest!
Oh, I can't get rid of it.
What?
Nothing I have will...
Alright.
Please don't kill me.
Duh!
I knew it.
Fucking bomb.
24 HP here.
Getting a little sketchy.
But the money is going up.
That's all that matters right now.
Flamoxium.
Hey, sir?
Boink!
I love doing those kills.
So satisfying.
I'm taking the flamox.
300 gold.
That could be alright for now.
But I really wanna find some levitation and go grab that demon eye.
What's that?
Polymorphine.
No thanks.
Like, this one has surprisingly big range.
Like, when you think it's not gonna hit, it usually does hit.
Polymorphine.
I'm squeezing the lemon here, I know.
I know.
But it's necessary.
Okay.
373.
I just want a single heart.
Is that too much to ask?
Just Uno.
Uno.
I wish I knew how to say heart in Spanish.
What's that?
Fungal Soil!
We getting high, boys!
On someone else's supply.
What's that whiskey?
Uh-oh, don't kill me.
Are you able to tongue me right up?
You are, okay.
Ah, that's scary.
Your HP.
It's a special horta.
Well, not that special.
Okay, I think it's time to leave.
We got a good amount of gold.
Can't be mad about that.
Salvaged a pretty shitty situation.
Ah-ha!
Good start.
That's also good.
Oh.
All right, all right.
And look at this.
Melee immunity.
We bleed... No, I don't want to bleed that.
We kick-steal extra damage and knockback.
I don't think so, man.
I think I gotta go with that.
I would be a fool not to take it.
Let me see my wands.
This is a good wand.
Actually a really good wand.
0.22, 0.38.
Okay.
Nothing amazing stats-wise on these.
But the spells are nice.
That one is on sale.
It contains a single one of those.
That could be nice.
But why not two of them?
And I also get some extra stuff.
Yeah.
Let's see it.
Probably make that better.
Not bad.
And a decent recharge here, actually.
Oh, this one has a mana charge speed of 250.
That's really decent.
This one- Ooh!
0.27.
This one is actually better.
Hold up now.
What do I want to get rid of?
Maybe just put these up here.
Dude!
That is so solid.
Look at that.
That's a really good one.
We've got our digging wand.
Very cool.
And this one reduces spread.
But adds castile.
Bum, bum, bum.
Ah, I kinda wanted to put them in there now.
Ah, that's okay.
But wait.
That's right.
It only works on the next one.
I discovered this last time.
Or at least I think I got to the bottom of that.
No, I didn't.
Do the math.
I don't have enough for this.
I wanted to buy this one as well.
Shit.
Well, I guess I can come back for it.
I don't know which one is best, then.
0.4-
That's actually not- That's actually really cool.
Like a little shotgunny.
Yeah, that's gonna be my wand.
Seems good to me.
And do I want to make Stuart mad?
Let's see here.
What if I hand him some whiskey?
Maybe he'll make peace with me.
Right?
If you give him a gift of whiskey?
Or I confuse him?
I'm at this level of frustration with this man that I'm considering such outlandish tactics.
Such as trying to flummox him.
Or offer him silver or gold in exchange for not messing with me.
Wait a minute.
Is this better?
It is not.
But the wand is good.
This is a good wand.
But hold on, eh?
Hold on a minute.
No, this is the one because of the- What if- What about a single one?
No, that's a bit too slow.
That's the one.
Yeah.
All right.
Let's leave.
I'm playing it super saviour.
I am gonna come back to buy those triggers though, as soon as I have the money.
And I have to remember, I am immune to melee.
I gotta review this stuff every time I leave a holy mountain.
I think it's a good practice.
Got a wand already.
Actually a decent wand too.
That's not bad at all.
It may even be better than this.
It is better.
Thanks.
And not- Oh man, I'm just- Oh my goodness!
I'm just being showered with rewards here.
What's going on?
Do I want this?
0.2, 0.15?
Could actually be okay.
Maybe for digging.
It is shuffle, but I think we're okay there.
This doesn't dig, right?
Unfortunately, my luminous drill will also dig through gold, so...
Where are you going?
Am I immune to fire with this?
Actually it does.
Cool.
The one upside of being slimy.
It's actually a decent wand that I have here.
It's really nice.
This I can do.
A circum?
No, lava.
Any water though?
Let's just grab that.
Unfortunately, I never found levitation, so I didn't grab the demon eye.
Okay.
Thought I saw something in there.
There's definitely something up here.
My senses are tingling.
This is kind of a shitty wand still.
I am really not a fan of the luminous drill.
It gets the job done in a pinch, but other than that, it's just utter trash for me.
Even if this was constant, it's still annoying to use.
Nah, there's nothing up here.
There is actually something up there.
That was a mistake.
The fungal caverns, I have returned.
They're all stuck up here?
Okay, I guess I'll leave them then.
I guess it is good for doing stuff like this.
Wow, zero castile.
Intriguing?
I don't know.
This is getting...
This is a little bit sketchy what I'm doing here.
Oh, no.
Oh, shit.
I'm phlamoxed.
Phlamoxium!
Flup, flup, flup, flup, flup, flup, flup, flumoxium.
It's going really bad.
Nooo!
Yeah, I think this is the start of the end.
Oh, I can't... I can't leave.
Oh yeah, this guy is too difficult.
Major mistake.
This place is nuts.
And I'm starting with polymorphine, just to rub it in.
That's just fantastic.
Oh man.
That's the classic fungal caverns experience.
Just from 0 to 100.
Really fast.
What's that?
Pheromone.
Oh actually, yes.
Although it will only come in handy at the Heezy base.
I didn't want to break the bottle.
Annoying little Huerta.
Just so annoying.
I will leave this here.
Of course it breaks!
I was trying to put it down gently.
That's fine.
I'm never going back up there anyway.
Man, this spell revealed a way bigger area than I thought here.
Like, look at all this here.
This I... What?
Why is all this revealed?
You can have a bomb.
I didn't get you, did I?
I did not.
I think I got him there though.
Not... Ah, close.
Whoa!
Oh my goodness.
There's two of them now.
How's this guy not dead?
Come here.
Oh my... Man, I hit this guy five million times.
Or maybe it was... Maybe they switched places and it was like some kind of illusion with his HP.
I'm actually just dying to these guys.
I refuse to give up.
They need to die.
Did he just kill himself?
I hope he did.
That would be very fitting.
I see wand, but I see whiskey and I see fire on both sides.
That means...
I think I can grab it and leave without anything happening here.
Look how fast I am.
Oh no.
Shit.
Ah, we gotta go.
We gotta go.
No, we don't.
We don't.
Somehow the fire stopped.
We were at like 70%.
I don't know how that just stopped.
Ah, but we gotta go.
Ah, shitty start.
Absolutely shitty start.
But it's okay because look at this.
Chainsaw for 20.
Small teleport for 30.
Somehow we get the stuff we need for the little money we have.
Lovely.
Attract gold, revenge bullets.
He returned fire when hit and gained 20%.
Fuck it.
Let's try it.
We're trying new things.
Maybe it's amazing.
Maybe the return fire we do is wildly good.
You know, maybe it will actually kick ass.
This one is way too fast.
That's actually too much.
That's a little bit detrimental here.
It's way too fast.
Hey.
Hello.
I want to keep this one.
Slime ball.
Shuffle.
Yeah.
I think I'm good.
We do have this though.
We already shoot so fast.
Don't even need one of them.
What, 15.
What does it look like if I do this?
Ah, it works.
Just not that great.
I'll keep it like this for now.
Yep.
Yeah, I'm not gonna anger anybody.
We're playing by the rules.
There's a fucking fly in my room.
Got through my window.
It's buzzing around me.
It's pissing me off.
At some point I gotta let it outside.
Oh, wait, I don't have water.
I want to save my pheromone.
Because it's like a guaranteed heal later.
Am
I noticing this revenge bullet?
It's a wand.
Mist of spirits.
Now, I actually like this as a digging wand right now.
That was almost disastrous.
This is the power of the starter wand here.
Let me go through the coal.
Fuck, this doesn't dig anywhere.
I guess I can... I'm gonna make a tunnel through the woods.
No, bury it.
Ah, fuck.
Uh, I guess I can maybe go here.
Yeah.
Shit.
Nope.
I could just go back, I guess.
I mean, this works.
It's a little bit scuffed, but uh, now I'm stuck here.
I thought it was being so smart.
Oh, right.
Well, that was a waste of time.
Give me money.
Oh, it doesn't dig there.
Okay, this digging wand is actually terrible.
I gotta go all the way around.
I need an empty bottle.
Again.
No, this is blood mist.
Why would I want that?
Can
I see you up?
I did see you there.
Ow!
Oh, no, I have no water.
Get to the water.
I forget I have teleport.
I actually forgot about that.
It sort of kicked in just now.
Are you not dead yet?
Uh, this is not going well.
Uh, there was water up here.
40 HP.
And not even that much gold.
Wow.
Uh, there's a wand.
Bunch of things on here.
I'm gonna replace my shitty digging wand with that.
And there's a chest too.
Ah, I was so excited.
Dreams are shattered.
Oh, but look at this.
Right when I get rid of my digging wand.
It's exceptional.
That's gotta be another one close by.
Or I can dig with this thing right here.
If I can do this correctly.
Actually, not bad.
Yeah!
Sweet cakes.
Oh.
Ah, fuck off.
No thanks.
So many chests, so little value.
Feels bad, man.
I really should start going back.
Chest.
But how do I get in?
Oh, a wand.
Huh.
Nah.
Can't even turn that into water.
Ow.
Nah, we leave.
Fuck this.
We're getting the hell out of here.
Yeah, 340.
Hopefully it's okay.
Man, luminous drills, huh?
Faster movement.
You know what?
Sure.
We're trying all the new things today.
Okay, it is faster, but it's not like...
Acceleration faster, but it's nice.
I appreciate it.
Okay, let's see if we can't do something neat here.
Do we have anything that will dig in these things, other than luminous drill?
Because I honestly hate it.
Ah, I guess not.
Why is this one 200, but...
This costs 400 usually?
Why?
It's not even that good.
I will buy this, I guess.
Replaces.
Put this one up here.
Actually, the wand is kind of bad.
I mean, you gotta have some digging.
You really do gotta have some digging.
Mana charge speed is 270 here.
Do we have anything higher?
That's like the thing I look for in the digging wand at this point.
It's really just that.
Like, this is oddly similar to the one we had before.
I'm gonna keep one up there.
We actually don't need this many.
Maybe that's a decent amount.
Now we're limited by recharge.
Now we're not.
That's good, I think.
That's a good amount.
Okay, then we have this thing right here, which is the big magic guard.
Eight guarding lights rotate around you for a time.
You know what?
Why don't we just try that?
Let's put that on.
Or do I want to replace... Yeah, this one sucks.
Okay, very interesting.
This actually looks kind of dope.
Like some kind of firework.
Let's try it.
We can teleport.
Oh, that's a terrible teleport wand.
I guess I could put it back here then.
Unless... Wait a minute.
The recharge time is the big... Oh, we can probably just take a different wand here.
That one.
Yes, that's cool.
I wonder if it blocks projectiles.
I do... Oh, you know what?
I wonder if it will kill Stuart.
I'm gonna try it, guys.
I feel like I'm not so too heavy about my perks anyway, so at this point, I'm just gonna spam this and go nuts on this guy now.
Get ready.
And worst case, I can teleport, so we're actually fine.
Yeah, stay mad.
Stay mad.
Oh, no, I'm stuck.
I'm stuck.
No, I'm stuck.
Come here.
Hey!
Oh, no.
Leave!
Fuck, these were... I had them in the wrong keybind.
Hey, Stuart.
I'm not done with you.
Look what I'm... I'm desecrating your temple, bitch.
Come here.
Good news is, I think it was working pretty well.
Fuck, wrong one.
Come here.
Oh, yeah, you mad, bruh.
Okay, wow, you have a lot of HP there.
Come on, man.
There we go.
Not too bad.
We got some extra gold here.
I think I'll just purchase something like this.
Oh, well, the problem is mana with that one.
Let me see here.
150... what is the best one?
Oh, man.
I kind of like this magic guard.
It's fun.
Yeah, neat.
We have a problem here, though.
Look at all this bone dust.
Eldritch portal.
I don't know about that, bro.
Not too intrigued.
Actually really cool.
And a prickly spore pod.
Ooh, mana charge speed, baby.
That's the one I need.
Hold up.
This is very promising.
Will you get away from me?
Let's see here now.
Put this on this guy right here.
No.
Maybe this?
Oh, that's...
Not too amazing.
Damn.
I thought that would be a lot better.
But maybe it's meant for this.
Kind of want to see what happens if I make this super...
I wonder how many of these I can have up at the same time.
Because they definitely stack.
Look.
As time goes on, the circle becomes less bright.
Until... So this is just one.
Look at that.
It doesn't even release any orange particles, but when I do multiple, it does.
I wonder if that's because they collide into each other.
Very cool.
Oh, that's faster.
Oh yeah, this is better.
Ah, cool.
All right, I think I like this.
It's pretty dope.
It's gonna be my weirdly... Maybe I'll try that as a build.
Think about it.
But I would like to put it on...
So that's not the issue there.
Let me try this.
We don't have enough mana?
That sucks.
Okay.
Oh well.
It's the worst digging wand ever, man.
Can I have an energy orb please or something?
I almost refuse to walk around with this because it's so bad.
I
don't know what my main damage wand should be here.
I don't like any of this.
Maybe I'll just brute force a bunch of these on here.
I mean, it's not bad.
It's okay.
Actually, do that.
Duh, duh, duh, duh.
Unless...
Okay.
Nah.
All right.
Keep it simple.
We are just in the second.
No, we're not.
We're in the third.
Oh, actually.
Does feel nice to move fast around.
I gotta say, this is actually super comfortable.
This is a perk I can get behind, I think.
Still missing water.
It's biting me hard in the ass.
Can I have an empty bottle please?
God, this weapon sucks.
You know what?
We're going all in on this.
This is my primary weapon now.
See, that's what I'm talking about.
That's the dig I was looking for.
Oh, that's an Ukuskivi.
We're not getting anywhere near there.
No, sir.
Uh-oh.
See how effective this is?
Hey, not bad.
It works in a pinch.
This is actually kind of fun.
I am kind of dying here though, because I don't have any water.
What is that?
It's like a salamander.
Please.
Thanks.
This is super effective against these guys.
Wow.
Does not absorb projectiles though.
This is honestly fun.
I love having this attack here.
But I think it is... We do have a lot of money.
I think it's time to move on.
Shit!
Yeah, yeah.
It may be over.
I gotta play this super carefully.
I can't go into open spaces.
Just keep digging.
Do not drown, please.
Maybe I can venture out in here.
Ah, that's too risky.
Fuck!
I figured that would happen somehow.
3 HP.
Ah, it's over, isn't it?
God damn Poland.
Okay, load up on this.
Wait, is this destroying the water?
What's happening here?
It's disrupting the water somehow.
That's funny.
Oh no.
Run!
Oh my god.
Oh no, it's these guys.
Step into my office.
Yes!
It was super effective.
Portal.
Got it!
Oh, that's right.
Get ready.
Let's see what we have.
Always cast mana.
I don't have enough money though.
Oh shit.
Welcome to my office.
Come here.
What the fuck is that one?
Oh, permanent shield.
Oh, I kind of want to grab that right now.
That would be glorious.
Come here.
Come here, bro.
Dude, the Poland is actually doing work.
Did I just discover the ultimate method?
Poland?
I gotta lure him closer.
Come on, you asshole.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Very nice.
This looks very promising.
Let's see what else we got.
Okay.
A bunch of bombs.
This though.
It does cast.
Oh, it does have a recharge time that is longer than, well, a very long time.
I couldn't make up something funny.
Let's grab it.
Because even though it has such a long cast time, maybe we can put it to good use somehow.
How can we possibly utilize this?
So it excels at casting a lot of spells in quick succession, right?
So if I have a lot of spells, maybe if I have spells that cost a lot, basically, that would be nice.
Nah, this is this.
Oh man, the wand sucks because of the recharge time.
That's so sad.
It really is sadness.
This one is really good.
Yeah, this wand right here is fantastic.
I don't want these.
Wait, autonomous rock ally.
With homing, maybe that could be fun.
How does that feel?
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
No, no, no.
Still a bit too slow.
What if I add this?
I want to make it mega fast.
Get rid of that.
Look at this.
I like the shield I have up here now and the shield inside.
It's kind of cool.
Maybe I'll go full on like melee, where I just run into enemies and they die.
Wouldn't that be kind of fun?
I think what I had before was actually just better.
Like this right here is solid.
Also, it's disrupting the water somehow.
It has a weird interaction with water.
Ah, I should have bought this and grabbed the...
Damn it, I should have grabbed the heavy spread there.
That could have come in handy here.
What if I do something like this though?
Because then it casts two at a time.
Still though, it is too slow.
Yeah, this is my primary damage.
It feels weird to say.
Also use that.
The digging here I'm still not a big fan of.
Let's do this instead.
I think that's better.
So this reduces recharge time.
I should put this here.
Oh yeah, look at that.
Now we're talking.
Maybe I want to experiment with this.
I feel like this should become a run where I just experiment with... Like this is already a cool new thing to try, right?
And look at this.
I have pheromone that I can use here.
But we got to get through out here first.
So we got to actually do this.
Oh yeah, I know you're angry.
Oh, this is...
Whoa!
Actually, this works really well in combination with the Poland, but...
If only we had a little ad mana there.
But take it back to... No, actually keep the luminous drill, because we are going to be in Heezy Base.
All right.
Okay.
Let's see how well this goes.
This is a very new tactic here.
I mean, it's doing not bad.
Just a very new play style here.
I got to get used to.
But I mean, it's kind of dope.
It doesn't destroy projector.
Uh, these things, that's kind of nice.
Uh oh.
Kind of fun.
But it's hard to keep them in the exact spot.
And I guess I am taking some damage here.
I need to get the fuck out of here and get some water.
Water!
I'm burning!
Fucking hell!
I got to find a friendo right now.
It's friendo time.
Don't!
My shield is helping out immensely here.
Friendo?
Friendo!
Come here!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, friendo!
You asshole!
I hate you for that.
This is actually incredible.
I'm liking this spell here, guys!
This is dope!
Somehow, this guy is taking very little damage, though.
What?
Whoa!
What the hell?
Friendos!
We got to wait for this to wear off.
I can't put them in danger like that.
Yes!
Both of them!
Heal me, guys!
Oh, that's lovely!
Come on!
He's actually burning!
Stop burning!
Look at him!
He's just wandering around like a headless chicken while he's burning.
And there it is!
Full HP!
Oh, no!
Immediately, I lost all my HP and Friendos died.
It's a hard knock life.
Gonna make some new friends.
Wait, why am I taking damage?
I think if I go too close to a wall, I take damage.
It's kind of odd.
Oh, look at this!
We're having a potay.
I can get in there.
I see an enemy.
A chest!
Uh,
what do we got?
Formation hexagon.
Liquid detonation.
Four seconds recharge, but it does have a sickly high mana charge speed.
Damn!
But it's kind of useless with that recharge.
There's way too much oil!
I'm gonna leave that guy.
You know what I think happens?
If they're actually in liquid, these projectiles move much slower, and maybe that's what does less damage to them.
Because I start doing a lot, and then suddenly they take no damage at all.
And it's usually when they drown themselves in their own urine or oil.
Same thing.
Don't you kill me.
I love trying these new builds here.
It's actually so good!
Super safe as well, because I can just like kill them through corners and stuff.
And it doesn't detonate explosives.
It's really nice.
Whoopsie daisy, but that guy does detonate.
I don't see a friendo.
Come on.
Nah, these guys just take very little damage.
Oh, actually that's scary, because that thing's gonna explode and I die.
Don't want to risk that.
One by one, we dismantled their entire operation here.
Haha, this spell is amazing!
I've been sleeping on this!
And I don't even think I have fulfilled.
No!
All right, that was the end of that.
Damn it.
Well, you know what?
Magic guard?
Holy fuck, what a spell.
What a spell.
I'm in love with that.
And you know what?
I haven't even potentially made that as good as it can be.
Imagine having zero castelae, zero recharge, add mana.
That thing is gonna charge up so fast.
It's gonna be insane.
I can't even imagine that.
That's incredible.
Okay, yeah, we're definitely just trying new things.
I'm gonna force myself to try a build with a new spell this time, that I haven't really tried to focus on yet.
Because I'm missing out on these things if I don't do it.
That was a lot of fun, man.
All right, well, we gotta go through the motions here.
Go through the hemisphere, collect the gold, find a heart, hopefully.
That would be stellar.
You can do that.
Man, my starter one really sucks.
Very slow.
Although, I have water though, so can you believe I didn't find a bottle the entire run?
Last time?
To put my water in?
If I had known I wouldn't have found that, I would have changed my pheromone for water for sure.
Guess I learned my lesson there.
Always change it to water.
Firebolt.
Yeah.
In fact, I'm gonna go up and grab the heart up there now.
I have the means.
Cheers, everybody.
I hope you're having a wonderful Saturday.
Oh,
yeah.
Is there anything better in this world than chilling out and playing games in the weekend?
I really doubt it.
But then again, I am a huge nerd.
Up.
And I'm taking the tablet here now as well.
Uh, no.
Thank God the mana recharge is fast enough.
Oh my God.
How are you kidding me?
Have you seen worse gameplay from anyone before?
Because this is actually peaking in that department of worst gameplay ever.
I can't believe that just happened.
Yeah, there we go.
And the tablet.
Come on.
What?
There we go.
Yoink.
Put it here.
Alrighty.
Decent start there.
Guaranteed.
Heart.
Oh, actually, I just had an idea.
Okay.
So obviously, we got to get demon eye and go to fungal caverns.
And we're gonna try to get high three times.
But I think whenever we do that, we got to come back here as well.
Maybe something will change on this stone when we come back.
Because when I tried translating this, it didn't make any sense at the time.
But maybe something more will reveal itself when we come back here.
After having done that.
Let's keep that in mind.
I think that could be something there.
Okay, so let me take a route.
Also, I'm gonna use my tablet now.
It's time to throw heavy things into faces of other living beings.
Never gets old.
You.
Oh yeah, that's so glorious.
Don't you fucking jump into me.
That was close.
Yes.
See ya.
A chest.
Look at me pro gameplay.
MLG 360 no scope.
420 crop rotation.
Concentrate a mana?
Sure.
I'll take that.
And I will bomb the shit out of this.
But
lovely.
Gold for me.
Great start so far.
Wow.
Miss one throw immediately get punished.
Okay, I tried.
Nice.
Now we're cooking.
Acceleratio too.
Let's just drink some of that.
I really did enjoy having that perk with the speed.
I'm gonna take that again if I find it.
Unless there's something better, of course.
But that was a surprisingly good perk.
And this too.
Oh man, dude, acceleration and that, you know what that means.
We go to the cave.
Oh yeah.
Did I just hurt myself with the tablet?
I threw it and then I was so fast because of the acceleration that I went in front of it.
And I took damage from it, I think.
That's teleportation.
That's a little bit not good.
No.
Okay, we're fine.
We're fine.
Look at that.
Teleportation just burns away.
Don't like that one.
The hell's going on there?
Oh, there's two minecarts.
He's trying to blow up my tablet.
Oh, he managed to hit me right in the face.
Very unfortunate.
No.
Dude, we're dying.
How?
My eye spots a little something.
Let's be careful here.
Okay, is that?
Oh, it's empty.
Uh, well, let me put this here.
And then I go in here.
Then I do this.
We steal all the oil.
Oh yeah.
Siphon it all up.
And then we deposit it right in.
Oh man, I'm slippery right now.
No, it's burning.
No, put it out.
Put it out.
Oh no.
That was a major mistake right there.
Hopefully I still have enough.
Stop burning.
That works.
Now eat this.
There we go.
Let's try again.
Come on.
Be enough, please.
Shit.
Fine.
Guess I'll find some more.
That's water.
Actually, give me some water.
I'm hyper fixated on that one right now.
We got a fine oil.
I feel like oil is plentiful.
There's always oil everywhere.
I see you down there.
Uh,
it's a bit risky.
Why is this guy not reacting at all to me?
I hear a fireman down there.
That is no bueno.
No bueno por favor.
Polymorphine is not what I want.
There's a chest as well.
A chest for me.
I'm never gonna get in there like that.
You know, this one is really good at dealing with enemies, so I should just use that.
Weird fungus.
Hold the phone.
We're getting high.
Right here, right now.
Drop everything.
We have a new main quest.
Let's go.
Eat, eat, eat.
Get rid of that pouch so we don't accidentally collect it.
Oh yeah, this should be enough.
Oh, we're over puking now.
Oh yeah, show me.
What do we got?
Diamond.
Wait, why am I burning?
I'm burning!
Oh, I'm 5 HP.
Oh, it's bad.
It's bad.
I'm gonna bomb my way in here and grab that chest and then I'm gonna make my way out, I think.
No, I'm definitely doing it.
Not, I think.
Acceleration was in there.
Fuck.
There's simply no oil when you need it.
It's kind of hilarious.
It's always there to be annoying, but not when you need it.
No, thanks.
Not really intriguing.
I think I just have to... yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Go!
Fuck everything.
We do have a lot of money, so we're fine.
That is a long-distance cast and a teleport.
What is that?
It's an acid cloud.
That's pretty cool.
Fire, immunity, yonk.
Grab it.
Grab that.
I'm gonna try the acid cloud.
I'm gonna try the double.
Never tried that one, right?
Gotta try the rock.
We're trying everything.
So this is obviously a total amazing thing that just happened, that we got this.
This is gonna change absolutely everything already, so that's fantastic.
Um, the torch?
Not really needed now.
Let's see here.
This is a shuffle wand.
Boo!
0.07, 0.75.
0.25.
I need, okay, I need to first of all determine my main.
And I did say I wanted to try a new type of damage, but I don't really have anything new.
I have this, but it's only eight shots of it, so you can't really use it.
Although,
nah, we're gonna go with spark bolt.
There's just no other real solution here.
That's a bit too slow.
It's probably this one.
Ah, the check, the mana recharge is terrible, but it is what it is, I think.
There's just not much to do about it.
That is more consistent, but I hate it.
Then we gotta go long distance cast teleport.
Also, it is just, yeah, it's a teleport.
It's not a small one, so let's keep that in mind.
That's actually a big problem.
Hopefully, we can find something else.
And for damage, I mean, I'm gonna replace these anyway, I guess.
Let's try that in here, or here.
We gotta try to make a cloud that will rain acid.
And look at this.
The whole fucking angry god situation completely circumvented, just like that.
Long distance cast teleport is the ultimate answer to a good run here.
Or to facilitate a good run, I should say.
I have water, I have concentrated mana and acceleration.
I have weird fu- ooh, I could get high again.
It is tempting.
Very tempting.
Then again, we do have a whole fungal cavern, if we really wanted to get high.
Oh, yeah, I can do this.
Okay, oh, that's the thing about the non-small one!
Escape!
Yeah, that's the problem with that.
Also, I just noticed that my wand sucks here.
I really need to change it.
I can't be running out of mana, it's just...
That's a huge problem.
It is so bad.
Actually...
Ah, this is also limited.
0.75.
I guess I gotta put it on this.
Oh, no, I mean, put this one here with that there.
And then these are gonna go here.
That's gonna be my teleport.
This is gonna be my damage.
On this one, we can put that there.
Sure.
Maybe even like that.
Yeah, why not?
Cool.
I- you know what?
Maybe I should bring some bombs instead.
Not a terrible idea.
Do that instead.
Just so we can make a couple holes in the terrain if needed.
Something down there.
Fuck.
Uh...
I guess I'm kind of stuck here.
Okay, watch this.
I'm gonna...
This is a bit of a risky move.
Wrong fucking button.
Oh, nice!
Didn't even see that!
The fuck?
Where was that?
Bomb down here?
No, we can teleport.
I just picked up a fucking heart.
And this one sucks.
Wow, it's bad.
I re- as soon as I find something else, I gotta go.
Oh my goodness, I can't kill anything.
It is so bad.
Okay, with patience, it's possible.
But this one is literally worse than a starting one right now.
Just because it's so slow.
Thanks!
Oh my god.
This is painful.
I'm just gonna look for a wand because this is actually just the worst.
I have no damage.
No!
Oh, you know what?
Guys?
You want to try this?
Oh, fuck!
Fuck!
It makes it above me.
I thought it would make it where I aimed.
Oh, I'm gonna die here, dude!
I can't kill these guys, man!
Where are the wands?
Show me the wands, damn it!
They're actually non-existent.
Oh, but I'm finding HP.
That's something.
There's a wand.
Please let it be good.
A hollow egg?
Nobody wants that.
I'll take it though.
I mean, it's really the best I have.
I just did a lot of damage.
Why are these not breaking open?
Dude, my eggs are doing more damage than my actual damage wand.
Oh, that's way too many there.
I can't kill them.
It's a bit risky just blinking through walls like that, but...
I guess I do have some money here.
Oh god.
Oh wait, I'm fire resistant!
I forgot about that part.
That makes me feel better now.
Shit.
Oh
god.
We're leaving, we're leaving, we're leaving.
Fuck this place.
Nope.
Please give me something good.
Okay.
Better.
Oh yes.
The energy orb.
We're cooking now.
Okay.
Gas fire.
Hey.
That's not bad.
Most projectiles are repulsed by your presence.
Um...
I think I'll take it.
And then I'll take...
that.
With...
What should be my primary damage here?
I mean, obviously I gotta go with this one.
And look at this, another long distance cast.
The hell.
What's this, circle of fire?
That seems satanic.
Might want more.
Let me start with this.
Let's see if we can't cook up something nice.
With what we've got here.
30 mana drain.
Holy inaccurate.
Oh, it has spread 18.
That explains it.
Now that runs out of mana too fast.
I think this is the one.
Oh, but wait, we do have add mana.
I kind of forgot.
Also very inaccurate.
Why is it so inaccurate?
The fuck?
Why is that inaccurate?
Oh, is it?
Wait a minute.
I think it's my repulsion field.
Oh no.
So the issue with this wand was the what?
Can I make it shoot faster?
Give me that one instead.
This is already a much better wand than what I had before.
But still kind of bad.
No, uh, wait, what?
No, this one.
Um...
Shit.
Okay, this adds castellate.
That's actually bad.
Maybe I load something in there.
Something like that.
It's a little slow, but it does...
Man, why is it so inaccurate?
Oh, this adds some spread, I guess.
Horrible.
Just horrible.
It's the repulsion field here is really messing with my aim.
Put this up here.
This is not the greatest wand.
This actually adds 0.42 castellate.
Maybe that's the issue here.
This actually allows to shoot a little faster.
You see that?
It's like double the damage output.
It's not great, but you know.
Better than nothing.
I don't even need Admana on that.
And that adds castellate, so...
Whoop-de-doo!
No, I gotta have this on a separate one, just for digging, I think.
And combine it with the Admana.
It's probably the best thing I can do here.
Even though it's shovel, it should be...
Oh, that's so inaccurate.
The spread on that is brutal.
Why is there a bomb there?
Oh, I just... I see, I see.
Uhhh, well...
I like it this way, I think.
It's not fantastic, but you know.
It is what it is.
Close quarters, respectable.
And this one is like okay for close quarter digging, I guess.
Yeah, that's okay.
That's fine.
Now, for the remaining money, I can't buy anything.
So we move on.
Okay, let's review.
Protectile, repulsion field, and fire immunity.
Right.
And I can get out.
Whoop!
Get me in!
Good.
Nah, not feeling that spell.
What's that?
Oh, it's a Kiva Skibi!
I'm immune to the Kiva Skibi.
Really low on money here.
Yeah, wait, this one is much better.
I'll be a little inaccurate.
But I'm fine with that.
So what time is it?
It's 10.
Okay.
Good.
I can go for a little longer.
Wow, massive hit on me.
Oh, is that an Uco?
Someone's doing electricity.
Where are you, bro?
It was that guy.
I have to remember, I have teleport.
I keep forgetting.
Getting in there with teleport is a little bit risky.
Get rid of that one.
I have no way of healing, so that's kind of a bummer.
What's this?
Oh, yeah, wait.
I forgot what it said.
Did it say diamond?
I think it's a diamond.
Oh, we have a worm.
Where's the worm?
It did not go through the brickwork here.
That's something.
Man, the repulsion field is saving my ass against these fuckers.
So big.
It's making up for my inability to dodge these attacks.
Sweet.
It's a big guy.
Oh, fuck.
No, he's 100% angering the gods.
There's no way he's not.
Kill him!
Whoa, he dropped the heart?
Yo, that's sick.
Also, there's something wrong here.
I can't fucking hit this guy.
There we go.
Did he actually dig all the way?
Uh...
I need to double check.
Sometimes the message doesn't appear unless you go far enough down.
Okay, so I think we're safe.
We seem to be okay.
I hear an uko skeevy, I think.
Ah, teleport.
If only that was a small one.
Hold on, I have to remember, I have this too.
It's kind of slow, but it works.
Oh, wait, that wand right there looks very intriguing to me.
That is a wand.
Oh!
Very inaccurate.
Why is it so... Oh, because of the...
Because of the repulsion field.
I mean, it's...
Despite everything, it's not the worst.
But it is really bad.
It's super hard to aim with.
That's pheromone.
I'm taking it.
We're going to be needing that in the next area.
This thing is going to be a little pain to deal with, I think.
Yeah, I don't think I can kill that right now.
Not reliably.
Uh, 360 money.
I think we gotta go.
We just have too little HP.
Wow!
Oh, energy shield!
I don't think I've seen that one before.
Teleporting cast.
Dude, there are so many.
What is this one?
Oh, Giga death cross.
That's plasma beam cross.
Explosion of spirits.
Wand radar.
I don't like any of these.
I'm going to save up and come back.
Okay, so.
This one?
How we got?
We got to get in water, I guess, for that.
This cost 30 mana, 10 damage.
It's so inaccurate.
I hate it.
Maybe it's okay to have it there.
Let me test.
Oh, I fucking hit a fish.
Let's try again.
Oh yeah, we can definitely utilize that.
Perfect.
Let's go grab 200 monies.
Oh, speaking of this thing.
If I find a black hole, I'm gonna try and bug this thing out again.
Remember that one time?
I want to see if I can replicate it.
Because it seemed kind of crazy.
Acid potion.
Have fun with that acid, boy.
Bye-bye.
Now we're in here.
We have pheromone.
So we can also heal with death.
It's actually...
It's looking good.
Even though the wand I have right now is absolutely trash.
Oh no!
Oh, I saw my own death briefly there.
Uh, maybe...
Ah, shit.
Yeah, I don't really have any damage here at all.
Are they fighting each other?
What's happening?
Yikes!
I want to puke when I see this damage.
Nasty.
We got the final wand right now.
That's a friendo.
But uh, yeah, we're full HP, so whatever.
Now the humanoids I don't have a problem with.
It's those damn robots.
More friendos up there.
Are we limited by mana?
No, it's the recharge.
Shit, how am I gonna...
Oh no.
Uh, destroy that.
Okay, okay, okay.
Yeah, this is this is not great.
Oh!
Wow!
The damage you do...
I can't kill him.
Riding on a train with no dough sucks.
What's up, man?
Got some friendos down there.
No!
God damn it.
There's no way I can...
Okay, let's do this carefully.
No, he's healing him.
He just killed his friend, by the way.
Why did I aggro him?
Ooh!
Look at all that freezing vapor.
Whoa!
Aww, I don't want to go through yet.
No way.
Where are the wands at?
Please, sir, show me the wands.
Damn it.
Oh, at least this guy can't turn around.
That's big.
There's a wand.
Ah, that's too much freezing vapor.
Let's wait it out.
Oh, he has a...
No!
Look at this pair of fucking trooper.
What are you shooting?
Whatever you're shooting, it scares me.
Show me what you got.
Energy spheres.
We gotta find some liquid now and heal.
I mean, we could just go back and heal, I guess.
Hey guys, this is for you.
He's getting a little scary here.
Oh, we're over... we're on the right side now.
Okay, okay, okay.
I see, I see.
Show me.
No, rocks.
It's not what a man needs right now.
Why is my wand black?
Look.
All right, it's healing time.
And it's re-roll time as well.
Hey!
Let's try this.
We're just stacking all the projectile repulsion shit stuff.
And there's also this one.
This is crazy.
All right.
Well, let's try this.
No.
No!
No, my field!
Wait a minute.
My my fucking field is working against me here.
Can you believe it?
How do I circumvent this issue?
Okay, watch this.
Oh, I need a small teleport for this.
I wanted to make a cool...
Shoot the heal, teleport into the heal type thingy.
Hey, wait a minute.
Aha!
Come on, get ready, get ready.
Did that heal me?
I stand on it, I kick it.
I shoot it.
Wait, that damaged me.
Okay, it's a bit of... that's not gonna actually hit me.
Too much of RNG there.
Hmm.
How do I solve this issue?
I guess I'm gonna just try again.
Oh, you know what?
Get slime.
Lots of slime.
Something more viscous.
Or I take a look over here.
What's this one again?
Ah, shit.
I don't have money for it.
Well...
Let me try again.
Maybe with... I don't have any acceleration left.
Damn it.
Ah!
Nah, I can't, I can't, I can't get it.
It moves away from me.
Duh!
Okay, what if I...
fall into it like that?
Watch.
Ah, wait, wait, wait.
Like this.
Watch.
Almost, almost, almost.
I need to be a little faster.
Little faster.
This is not gonna work.
Ah, it's annoying, man.
Can I really not heal?
Oh god, this guy's coming in here now.
Maybe I'll just move to the next.
Come here.
Bro, are you for real?
Nah, that's gonna take forever.
See ya.
Nobody has time for that.
My only hope right now is to find a friendo.
Operation use healing bolt has failed.
Look at all the shields I have.
Oh, this guy's a wand.
Um...
I'm scared.
That's how you do it.
Matter eater.
No.
I'm not feeling that wand.
Look at this, is it closed off?
I mean, I guess I can just...
All right, we're gonna get high in here.
It's eating time.
Come on, get it out.
Puke it.
Water.
Uh-oh.
Oh yeah, thank god.
Okay, something else became water.
That's good though.
I'm happy with that.
Let's just try and pay attention to what actually became water.
We could... I don't want to leave.
I have no money on me.
We got to find some money at least before we go out of here.
Some money.
It's got to be somewhere.
Yikes.
Whoa.
Scary.
Got him.
Man, what became water?
Friendo!
Come here, come here.
No, no, no, no, no.
Okay, let me kill him first.
Yeah, come here.
Shower with me.
Yes!
Oh, lovely.
You're the best.
Oh, it bounces up.
Let me get a little closer.
There you go.
Oh, doesn't that just feel amazing?
A little lower.
There we go.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's the spot.
Oh, yeah.
A little to the right.
Harder.
There we go.
Lovely stuff.
Thanks.
I'll see you later, bro.
Been a huge help.
Uh, I'll leave that guy alone.
Whoops.
Hold on.
How much can I absorb?
Oh.
No, friendo.
I have immense absorption.
Incredible.
Like, it feels bad right now because I don't really have a good wand.
But once I get that wand, oh man, I'm gonna be shitting on people.
There's gonna be poop everywhere.
Feces left and right, baby.
Just you wait.
Uh, that's a bit risky to go through.
Let me go up here instead.
And then we destroy that.
Special tactics.
You make base, you defend base.
That's white run.
The wise words of a now retired Ukrainian...
Named... Oh, I got his name, actually.
It's real name, but...
A real legend.
On the scene.
This is looking not good.
Just gonna get out of that.
Wait.
Smash that one.
And then we get out.
Hey!
It actually really, uh, helpful against these guys.
Yeah.
Dope.
Man, where are all the wands?
I feel like I've had terrible luck with finding wands.
There's just none.
Okay, I'm not invincible.
Calm down.
It's very close, though.
Propane tanks.
Gone wild.
Hey, that's for you.
No.
Ah, whatever.
I'm getting the money.
Oh, I'm scared of that.
Oh, wait, was that a friend?
Whoops.
He was so bloodied up, I couldn't see the color of his gun.
Alright, a thousand gold is definitely working here.
Now I just need wands!
Man, the big guy just won't die.
Oh, there's a friend.
Come here.
No, he's stuck.
Oh, no, he died.
Crap.
Where'd you come from?
What a mess!
Oh, we're leaving.
We're leaving.
Yeah, that... no way.
I just don't have the damage output for something like that.
I do not.
I did not hit her.
I did not.
Oh, hi, Mark.
All right, I think it's time.
Let's leave.
Solid.
Although actually not solid, because there was a couple spells I wanted to buy in the last Holy Mountain.
Why didn't I think?
Eh.
Let's see if there's something good here, though.
And now we're talking.
Okay.
Let's see here.
Extra knockback on spells.
You believe... I'm already immune to fire.
Yeah, I don't know about that.
Teleport... no.
Hmm.
Yeah.
Why not?
That's not too bad.
This one, though.
That's the one I want.
Ah, first.
My issue is that I have shitty wands.
Do we have better wands?
Fuck, I really wish I had taken that reduced recharge time in the last Holy Mountain.
Now, this one has very good stats, but it's shuffle, unfortunately.
Maybe that's not too bad.
You know what?
I did say I want to try and make a wand out of some new spells.
It's got to be this one.
The Cursed Sphere.
Why not?
Let me replace... actually, none yet.
Put this up here.
Ah, Cursed Sphere.
It does 15... it does cost 40, but... oh, but wait.
This is the one that makes rain clouds, right?
That does electricity, which is kind of bad for me because it does it irregularly.
And it could mess me up.
If I'm not careful.
So that makes me very unhappy.
This wand, though, is not the worst.
We can work with that, I think.
We add some damage here.
Shield up.
We also have an add mana if we need.
Add something like that.
And why not something like that?
Let's just see.
Not bad.
Not bad at all, actually.
Ah, I don't have the slots for this.
How much damage is this?
Oh, hello!
What the hell?
There's a tree in here!
Weird.
Ah, I think that's my wand for now.
Probably I'll find better stuff...
in this place, and then I can come back and change it.
Yeah.
That seems good.
Let's just leave it like that.
The healing's still kind of useless to me.
I need to find something that will slow down that projectile.
Like boomerang or something.
I like it.
Yeah, that's fine.
Let's go.
Whoa, what a start!
Amazing.
Not exactly what you were looking for.
That's an intriguing wand.
No, it's not.
Only two slots.
Oh no, we've got spiders.
And I do not kill them very easily, it seems like.
Okay, never mind.
It's not bad.
But the big spiders, that's the issue.
Huh!
That's kind of interesting in combination with the dropper bolt.
Let me see how that looks.
Huh!
Wow!
Hey, that's uh...
That's really cool.
Oh, but wait a minute.
It's shuffle.
So it wasn't even applying it there.
I think it's just my...
It's my projectile repulsion field that did it.
So I haven't even seen this in action.
I'm just gonna keep using it.
It's pretty dope.
Not so much damage.
All I need now is to find unlimited spells and I'm golden.
I mean, probably gonna be hard, but still.
That option is there.
Berserkium.
I think I would like that.
Thanks.
Yeah, it's so good.
The dropper bolts.
I guess I do also have Berserkium on.
What the hell?
Whoa!
Oh, it's shuffle though.
This would have been such a sick wand.
Dang it.
Nice.
But I guess it's better than this one.
This will take it.
What the fuck?
Okay, bunch of ones here.
This is great.
Sparkbolt with trigger is very welcome, in fact.
I like that.
That's already gonna make everything a lot better.
That worm is scary because he may anger the god.
Ooh, look at that mana max.
With glueball.
It was tempting to try.
Oops, why did I just do that?
Mistakes were made.
I'm releasing way too many of these.
Plasma beam.
Oh, that one is not bad either.
That's basically a way better version of this wand.
No, it's not way better.
It's okay.
Show me.
This is actually big.
No, it's not.
I take it back, it sucks.
I need to find a way to get up to the surface.
Man, why can't I fly that much?
What's happening?
Oh, maybe I just didn't give it enough time to reload.
That's just odd.
Down.
Oh, I'm here again.
Okay, fine.
Just go through that cursed shit.
He didn't die from that.
The big dropper bolt.
He survived it.
Wait, what?
Oh.
I was like, they don't drop any money.
And then it dawned on me.
I'm scared.
Okay, somehow I'm doing it.
I don't know how.
Things are coming together here.
Decent amount of money here.
What do we have here?
Orbit Larpa makes four copies of a projectile rotate around it.
Wouldn't that be kind of sick with the healing?
Essence to power.
Give it to me.
I will try it.
Okay, this worm needs to die.
Do not anger the gods, sir.
There's the pile of gold over here, thanks.
My problem right now is that I would love to find a way back to the surface, but if I do that, I'm gonna anger the gods.
And I feel like as soon as I start angering the gods without having the...
piece with gods perk, it's just...
The run is busted.
Like, I can't do anything.
It's just these guys that pop up are just too fucking good, you know?
So I'm basically stuck in this kind of limbo where I don't really want to go up, but I have to go up at some point.
So I gotta find a way to become more powerful before I do it so I can actually kill these...
gods that are appearing.
Or these god henchmen.
Henchmen of the gods.
That's a sick want.
No, it's not.
I'm playing this a little bit risky here for sure.
Why won't you die?
Also, not a single heart down here.
This is very unheard of.
Oh no, he's gonna spawn these guys, no?
What?
This guy is homing rocks.
That scares the fuck out of me.
Oh, I hate that.
Bro, I need that wand immediately.
You understand?
You hear me.
Oh, I think he ran out of them.
He doesn't have any more.
It's empty, bitch.
Did he die?
No, look, he's useless.
Yeah, he ran out.
This seems like something I would do.
I think I had because I remember my rocks being glowy.
Huh.
Three recharge though, that's terrible.
Oh no, it's the poison man.
He's come to poison me and all my friends.
Excuse me?
I'm getting good money though.
I am so ready for the next holy mountain.
God damn, I'm gonna be splurging.
I'm actually dying here.
There's a wand up there.
I really need to check it.
Anti-homing.
Maybe that can work with my healing.
No, because no.
That would require an enemy to be nearby, I guess.
And that's not very reliable.
I think I'm leaving.
I have so much money and I don't need anything from my current holy mountain.
Not that I remember at least.
Shit, shit, shit, shit.
Uh...
Let me see what's on here.
Sawblade.
That's what I need, baby.
Wait, that's an option?
Jesus.
So many magic arrows.
What the fuck?
Yo, this wand is crazy.
Look at the stats.
Look how many slots.
Always casts magic missile.
Converse any nearby...
That's insane.
Wait, where's my... didn't I...
Fuck.
If I only... I had brought the homing.
If only I brought the homing.
But I'm gonna use this.
That's a certain way.
Shit, he's coming.
Run!
Okay, get it, get it.
Uh... put it, put it, put it, put it, put it, put it, put it.
Uh... here.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Wait, what, wait, wait.
Hold on, something's wrong.
Hide behind here.
Quick, quick, quick.
Uh... there.
Yeah, that's right, bitch.
Run!
Hey, bitch.
Yeah, you like that?
Dude, my repulsion field is saving my ass.
This guy is no chill.
Am I even hitting him?
I am.
I got him.
Fuck you!
Amazing.
Whoa, look at this.
Someone has their way back.
No, I don't.
What, what?
Why doesn't that work?
Hey!
Nice!
That's really awesome.
Okay.
Now, let's see the perks.
Stainless armor, extra item in Holy Mountain.
My mana loca.
What?
You're currently hell of a mountain, loses half its cost, but gains more mana.
No.
No!
Yeah, I'll take this.
Thanks.
I will, uh, do that.
That seems good.
Okay.
Actually, there's also a sob lead on this one.
I should have just bought this one, actually.
I didn't notice.
Whoops.
This one, though?
It's crazy.
Especially because I have that mana.
Fuck yeah!
Let's make a neat pile of magic bolt with triggers here.
Keep everything neat and organized.
Let's put something like that there.
Actually, keep this one.
That's a good one.
Gunpowder trail, leave it here.
Wait, is that, what was that?
Wait, oil trail!
It could be kind of cool, because I'm immune to fire, right?
And yeah.
But then again, I now I kind of don't want to have any, uh, stains on me.
So maybe splashing oil everywhere is probably not the best idea.
Okay, look at all these slots!
Wild.
So we're gonna do this.
We're gonna do that.
That, that, that.
Let's put this over here.
Sawblade, whatever.
Trifurcated.
A dormant crystal.
Now the question is, what do I want to use?
So these cost...
How much was it?
This is 30 mana.
How much is this?
40, okay.
Actually, I do want to grab the Trifurcated.
Put it there.
Trifurcated pattern.
What should I put in here?
That.
And...
I, okay, this is gonna add...
Here's the thing.
If I use a trigger into some kind of big damage here, the optimal way to do this is actually not to use small spells inside of this package.
You want to do heart-hitting shit.
Like, what is the most heart-hitting that I have?
Oh, and this also, also always casts the thingy.
Let me see how that looks.
I had trouble saying that just now.
Wait, Castile?
What do you mean?
Oh!
Really?
I guess I have to get rid of that Castile.
Would love to have that quick recharge now that I left behind.
Oh, this one reduces Castile.
That's a little faster.
It's about the same.
Maybe don't add this then, because it adds Castile.
But so does this, I guess.
No, that's not, that's not, that's no fun.
Why am I constantly slippery?
Oh, this oil.
I don't know what to put inside of here.
Maybe this one also adds Castile.
Why is, why is the Castile so bad?
It's like 0.17.
Is it really that bad?
I guess add mana adds some.
That adds some.
Okay, this one removes some.
Add some adds.
Yeah, okay, fair.
Fair enough.
So maybe the answer here is not to go...
trigger.
Maybe we do something more simple here.
Let me just see.
Okay.
So it always shoots this magic missile, right?
I wonder if that is inherently adding to it as well.
Oh man, I'm getting lost in the weeds here again.
It's too damn slow.
So if I don't add anything,
there's no way it's that slow.
Recharge time is 0.3.
What?
Okay, it's gotta be adding it without telling me.
So I'm thinking this guy right here.
Oh look, it adds one seconds of Castile.
That's terrible.
Fuck me, man.
That just ruined this wand.
Well, unless I can get rid of it, of course.
Let me see what's on these other ones.
All adds Castile.
God damn it.
What a bummer, man.
I guess I'll have to give up on the dream of using this wand.
I'll have to go back to my other wand.
Shit.
What a bummer.
But I guess it's nice that it always casts magic missile.
I mean, that is kind of a big damage, right?
It's not bad.
So if I put something else big on this, like what is really big?
Okay.
I guess the saw blade.
Hold on, let me check something here then.
So if I take this now, saw blade orbit and put it on that bad boy right there.
With nothing else, will it apply it to the thingy?
It will!
Interesting.
I always thought the magic missile here, when it says always casts, that it would cast it first thing.
But if I just do it like this...
Yeah, it doesn't work.
You need to put it on some kind of spell.
All right, all right, all right.
I can work with that.
So what if I do this, just a simple trigger?
So here, look, here it does shoot the spell first and then the energy orb is being shot at the same time.
Isn't that weird?
I'm trying some things here.
It helps a little bit.
Nah, nah, it sucks.
It's really bad.
Unless I just go full Insano mode here.
Triple, triple, and we just put everything in we can.
It's gonna be the ultimate one-hitter.
I mean, that could be a thing.
In fact, I don't even have enough spells for that.
Maybe with this, what is that?
Orbit Larpa makes four copies of a projectile.
Hold on a second here.
I have ideas.
Imagine this.
Let me just get rid of some of these.
I have a great idea, I think.
And we're gonna take this one too.
Switch it back.
Now here.
If I now add this.
Right?
Was that gonna make four copies of the fucking magic missile?
I think it is.
Look at that, 255.
Oh my lord.
See, now we're starting to have a conversation about things here.
I am liking.
Likey-likey.
I also put saw blade on it.
It's gonna be wild.
We put all the things on it.
Essence to power, why not?
Yes.
How much?
Four thousand damage!
Say, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What?
Oh, based on the number of creatures, there must be a ton of creatures then.
Hold on, let me go to the left.
I wanna see how much that does over here.
Hold up now.
Four thousand!
Brother!
We're cooking!
Somehow!
Things are looking up.
Oh, oh!
How the fuck?
He just took all of my damn HP.
What an... I didn't even look here.
I was looking somewhere else on the screen.
Bro, are you actually kidding me?
Okay.
Uh...
Wow, that's crazy.
Let me just throw on a saw blade orbit as well while we're at it.
And another saw... Can I... Can I do this?
What if I just go omega nuts?
This is a very consistent 4k damage.
It's very odd.
But if I remove this...
It's like 2k damage.
Why is that?
Oh, it's...
I'm not sure why that is.
Hold on, let me remove these again.
180.
What is doing it?
It's gotta be the, uh...
It's gotta be this one.
That's insane!
Right.
Uh, what happened to... Oh, this one.
Yeah, that's the one that's really... It's just doubling the damage.
Somehow.
Okay.
But here's the thing.
We're not done.
We're... We're doing this again.
Whoa.
Wait, did I just do so much damage?
It didn't even register?
What's happening?
Let me see over here.
How much?
Wait, how much?
2000.
Hmm.
I mean, you can definitely... Okay, I run out of mana quick though with that.
That's maybe not the best thing ever.
Okay.
Is that another one?
I can't buy it though.
I don't have money for it.
No, there's also this one.
Spells to power.
Let me try this one as well.
Converge any nearby projectiles cast by you into extra damage.
Since I have this one, Orbit Larpa.
Let me try and get rid of one of these.
Otherwise, we don't have mana.
Uh, ah, fuck.
We gotta go left I guess.
Check this.
Oh!
Uh...
All right.
I don't know what's happening.
The game is having some issues.
I have broken the game.
With my ultimate wand.
I don't know what to do.
Oh no, uh, this looks like Rip.
This looks like Rip.
So why can I hear water running?
I may have to hold that for this.
Close the program.
And down it goes.
Hopefully, it's fine.
Oh no.
Autosave found.
Looks like the game crashed.
Should the... yeah, restore I guess.
Oh no.
What the... okay, well.
We are in the vaults.
I have no idea how.
And I don't know.
What... what wands do I even have?
I don't even have any...
Yeah, I just almost killed myself there.
That was bad.
The fuck?
Oh yeah, just do this.
Do this.
No!
Wait, what?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
It's gone.
Are you kidding me?
No.
All right, let's see how good this wand is.
All right, he died.
He died.
What else do we have?
I need to hit them.
Otherwise, I won't... wait, what was all the damage?
I was promised...
4000 damage.
Where is this damage?
Now we may be talking.
Hold on.
What is... what is...
Oh, wait a minute.
Oh, the orbit larber is on this one now.
It's not on the...
Oh, what?
Okay, that explains it, I guess.
Everything is fucked.
Yeah, honestly, just kill me.
Fucking crash, man.
I have no idea what just happened.
I think the holy mountain is gone.
Like what?
That was so weird.
I can't explain it.
Damn.
Okay, uh, it is...
Okay, yeah, I gotta stop now.
Kind of a good time to stop anyway, I guess.
So I'm not gonna have too much time to chat here.
I will say, uh...
tomorrow we do more Slay the Spire and I'm looking forward to it.
So for those that are following that, uh, you can check that out.
Approximately same time, I would say.
Maybe even a little bit earlier.
And after this, I will release some more prey for those that are following that as well.
Uh, otherwise, was everything working fine?
The whole mountain is gone.
Exactly.
Yeah, because when I teleported through the thingy, the portal, I appeared in nowhere.
Fuck everything, the run.
Yeah, that was a crazy run.
Okay, so I'm gonna go eat some food now, and I will see you guys tomorrow.
Sorry for the short chat.
I went a little over time, actually.
I was planning to stream for three and a half hours, so a little too much, but that's fine.
The one was so powerful, it annihilated the entire arena.
The entire area.
Exactly.
I broke the game.
I'm too good.
Yeah, all right.
I will dip out.
Uh, let's raid someone before I go here.
Who's doing anything in Noita right now?
I'm just gonna send it over to the first person.
Furyforged is playing, but...
Yeah, I'm gonna send you over to Furyforged.
He's probably doing something crazy again.
Thanks for watching.
I'll see you guys next time.
Bye-bye.